prettymay.net 2014-12-01

# PrettyMay Call Recorder for Skype, Call Center for Skype, Skype PBX, Skype recorder, Record Skype calls, Skype for business, free trial

|  | Privacy Policy  
---  
PrettyMay Inc. provides this website as a public service. We do not collect personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.  
**Information Collection and Use**  
The only information that are collected and stored automatically are the following: the IP address from which you access the internet, the date and time, the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website, the name of the file or the words you searched, and the browser used to access our website. This information is used to measure the number of visitors to the various sections of our website and identify system performance or for server issues. We also use this information to help us expand the coverage of the website and to make the website more useful.   
**Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies by themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are configured to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies.   
**Security**  
PrettyMay maintains this website. For website security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we use software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Causing damage to computer systems is a violation of US law and is subject to criminal prosecution.   
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "Last Updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. In the event of a material changes to this Privacy Policy, a prominent notice will be placed on this web site. If the change involves personally identifiable information, the notice will contain instructions on how you can opt-out of such use.   
**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](mailto:contact@prettymay.net) at any time.  
Version: 1.0 Date: 12/20/2007
